Norman Vincent Peale Papers
Norman Vincent Peale Papers
- I. Correspondence
  - B: Special correspondence
    - Norman Vincent Peale correspondence
      - Correspondence, 1946
        - Associate Ministers (Box I:B:25)
        - "Attack" Mail (Box I:B:25)
        - Baptisms (Box I:B:25)
        - Bills - Ketchum (Box I:B:25)
        - Blanton, Dr. Smiley (Box I:B:25)
        - Book Correspondence (Box I:B:25)
        - Budget (Box I:B:25)
        - Christian Endeavor (Box I:B:25)
        - Church Clinic (Box I:B:25)
        - Classis (Box I:B:25)
        - Collegiate Church Office (Box I:B:26)
        - Comments (Box I:B:26)
        - Consistory (Box I:B:26)
        - Constitutional Government; A-Z; Dr. Rumely (Box I:B:26)
        - Easter (Box I:B:26)
        - Elberon Church (Box I:B:26)
        - Every Member Canvas (Box I:B:26)
        - Illustrations (Box I:B:26)
        - Ketchum, M.D. - Treasurer (Box I:B:26)
        - Members, New (Box I:B:26)
        - Men's League (Box I:B:26)
        - Mobilization (Box I:B:26)
        - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box I:B:26)
        - New Book (Box I:B:27)
        - Ocean Grove (Box I:B:27)
        - Pawling (Box I:B:27)
        - Peale Family (Box I:B:27)
        - Peale, Dr. C.C. (Box I:B:27)
        - Peale, Rev. Leonard (Box I:B:27)
        - Peale, Norman Vincent, Personal (Box I:B:27)
        - Peale, Dr. Robert C. (Box I:B:27)
        - Peale, Robert W. (Box I:B:27)
        - Peat, Harold W. (Box I:B:27)
        - Peck, George (Box I:B:27)
        - Pettingill, Samuel B. (Box I:B:28)
        - Presbyterian Ministers Fund (Box I:B:28)
        - Princeton Conference Group (Box I:B:28)
        - Reader's Digest articles (Box I:B:28)
        - Reader's Digest letters, "Faith for Today" (Box I:B:28)
        - Rotary (Box I:B:29)
        - St. Nicholas Church (Box I:B:29)
        - St. Nicholas Church (Clarke) (Box I:B:29)
        - Script - "Gun Glory" (Box I:B:30)
        - Servicemen's Committee (Box I:B:30)
        - Soldiers Mail (Box I:B:30)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, A-Q (Box I:B:30)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, R-Z (Box I:B:31)
        - Special Work Committee (Box I:B:31)
        - Staff Memos (Box I:B:31)
        - Stafford Family (Box I:B:31)
        - Summer Supplies (Box I:B:31)
        - Sunday Memos (Box I:B:31)
        - Twenty-fifth Anniversary (Box I:B:31)
        - 250th Anniversary (Box I:B:31)
        - Woman's Home Companion Letters (Box I:B:31)
        - Y.M.C.A. (Box I:B:31)
      - Correspondence, 1947
        - Advertising (Box I:B:32)
        - American Magazine (Box I:B:32)
        - Associate Ministers (Box I:B:32)
        - "Attack" Mail (Box I:B:32)
        - Bills (Box I:B:32)
        - Book Comments (Box I:B:32)
        - Book Correspondence (Box I:B:32)
        - Book Lists - Mailing Lists (Box I:B:32)
        - Budget (Box I:B:32)
        - Budget Letters (Box I:B:32)
        - Budget Lists (Box I:B:32)
        - Classis (Box I:B:33)
        - Church Clinic (Box I:B:33)
        - Clinic (Box I:B:33)
        - Collegiate Church - Letters of Transfer (Box I:B:33)
        - Collegiate Church Photos (Box I:B:33)
        - Collegiate Church Office (Box I:B:34)
        - Comment, Letters of (Box I:B:34)
        - Consistory (Box I:B:34)
        - Constitutional Government (Box I:B:34)
        - Easter (Box I:B:34)
        - Education (Box I:B:34)
        - Elberon Church (Box I:B:34)
        - Every Member Congress (Box I:B:35)
        - Farm Journal Articles (Box I:B:35)
        - Farm Journal Letters (Box I:B:35)
        - Foreign Mail (Box I:B:35)
        - Guide to Confident Living (Box I:B:35)
        - Illustrations (Box I:B:35)
        - Ketchum, Milton, Treasurer (Box I:B:35)
        - Men's League (Box I:B:35)
        - Mobilization (Box I:B:35)
        - Ocean Grove (Box I:B:35)
        - Organ (Box I:B:35)
        - Original List - New Members (Box I:B:35)
        - Pawling (Box I:B:36)
        - Peale Family - Other Members (Box I:B:36)
        - Peale, Dr. C.C. (Box I:B:36)
        - Peale, Rev. Leonard (Box I:B:36)
        - Peale, Norman Vincent - Personal (Box I:B:36)
        - Peale, Dr. Robert W. (Box I:B:36)
        - Peat, Harold R. (Box I:B:36)
        - Peck, George (Box I:B:36)
        - Presbyterian Minister's Fund (Box I:B:36)
        - Princeton Conference Group (Box I:B:37)
        - Reference Letters (Box I:B:37)
        - Reformed Church (Box I:B:37)
        - Rotary (Box I:B:37)
        - St. Nicholas Church (Box I:B:37)
        - Sears, F.M. (Box I:B:37)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected (Box I:B:38)
        - Soldiers Mail (Box I:B:38)
        - Special Work Committee (Box I:B:38)
        - Staff Memos (Box I:B:38)
        - Stafford, Rev. F.B. (Box I:B:38)
        - Stafford Family (Box I:B:39)
        - Summer Supplies (Box I:B:39)
        - Sunday Memos (Box I:B:39)
        - Testimonials (Box I:B:39)
        - Thanksgiving Day Service (Box I:B:39)
        - Western College (Box I:B:39)
        - Wheeler, Howard (Box I:B:39)
        - Women's Home Companion letters (Box I:B:39)
        - Women's Home Companion, favorable (Box I:B:39)
        - Women's Home Companion, unfavorable (Box I:B:39)
        - Y.M.C.A. (Box I:B:39)
      - Correspondence, 1948
        - Advertising (Box I:B:40)
        - American Magazine Articles (Box I:B:40)
        - Articles by Dr. Norman Peale (Box I:B:40)
        - Associate Ministers (Box I:B:40)
        - Blanton, Dr. Smiley (Box I:B:40)
        - Blanton, Dr. Smiley - Problem Letters (Box I:B:40)
        - Book Correspondence (Box I:B:40)
        - Boyer, Merce (Box I:B:40)
        - Budget (Box I:B:40)
        - Budget Letters (Box I:B:40)
        - Church Bills (Box I:B:40)
        - Classis (Box I:B:41)
        - Clinic (Box I:B:41)
        - Collegiate Church (Box I:B:41)
        - Collegiate Church - Letters of Transfer Comments (Box I:B:41)
        - Consistory (Box I:B:41)
        - Dewey - Presidential Campaign (Box I:B:41)
        - Edgar, Albert - Active File (Box I:B:41)
        - East Orange (Box I:B:41)
        - Easter Offering (Box I:B:41)
        - Employment Committee (Box I:B:42)
        - Farm Journal (Box I:B:42)
        - Foreign mail (Box I:B:42)
        - Guide to Confident Living (Box I:B:42)
        - Illustrations (Box I:B:42)
        - Infant Baptisms (Box I:B:43)
        - Ketcham, Milton D. (Box I:B:43)
        - Liberty Magazine (Box I:B:43)
        - Men's League (Box I:B:43)
        - Miller, O.R. (Box I:B:44)
        - Ocean Grove (Box I:B:44)
        - Pawling (Box I:B:44)
        - Peale Family (Box I:B:44)
        - Peale, Dr. C.C. (Box I:B:44)
        - Peale, Rev. Leonard (Box I:B:44)
        - Peale, Norman, correspondence (Box I:B:44)
        - Peale, Norman, personal (Box I:B:44)
        - Peale, Mrs. Norman V. (Box I:B:44)
        - Peale, Robert W. (Box I:B:45)
        - Peat, Harold R. (Box I:B:45)
        - Peck, George (Box I:B:45)
        - Prentice-Hall (Box I:B:45)
        - Problem Mail Sent to Kenneth S. Giniger (Box I:B:45)
        - Presbyterian Ministers' Fund (Box I:B:45)
        - Princeton Conference Group (Box I:B:45)
        - Proposed New Folder re: Church References (Box I:B:45)
        - Reformed Church (Box I:B:45)
        - Rotary (Box I:B:45)
        - St. Nicholas (Box I:B:46)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected (Box I:B:46)
        - Special Work Committee (Box I:B:46)
        - Spiritual Mobilization (Box I:B:46)
          See also Mobilization (Box I:B:15)
        - Staff Memos (Box I:B:47)
        - Stafford Family (Box I:B:47)
        - Summer Supplies (Box I:B:47)
        - Sunday Memos (Box I:B:47)
        - "Too Many Churches," American Magazine, June 1948 (Box I:B:47)
        - United Advance Fund, R.C.A. (Box I:B:47)
        - Western College (Box I:B:47)
        - Woodbury, Clarence (Box I:B:47)
        - Y.M.C.A. (Box I:B:47)
      - Correspondence, 1949
        - Advertising (Box I:B:48)
        - American Bible Society - Mr. Fehlam (Box I:B:48)
        - American Magazine (Box I:B:48)
        - American Magazine article fan mail, etc. (Box I:B:48)
        - Articles by Dr. Norman Vincent Peale (Box I:B:48)
        - Birthday Greetings (Box I:B:48)
        - Blanton, Dr. Smiley (Box I:B:48)
        - Books Received (Box I:B:48)
        - Boy Scouts (Box I:B:49)
        - Boyer (Box I:B:49)
        - Budget Letters (Box I:B:49)
        - Charlotte Observer (Box I:B:49)
        - Chicago Daily News (Box I:B:49)
        - Classis (Box I:B:49)
        - Clinic (Box I:B:49)
        - Collegiate Church (Box I:B:49)
        - Collegiate Church Letters of Transfer (Box I:B:49)
        - Column Clippings, "Confident Living" (Box I:B:49)
        - Column Mail, Confident Living (Box I:B:50)
        - Comments (Box I:B:50)
        - Consistory (Box I:B:50)
        - Constitutional Government, Dr. Rumely (Box I:B:50)
        - Dickler, Gerald, Attorney (Box I:B:50)
        - East Orange, New Jersey (Murphy) (Box I:B:50)
        - Easter (Box I:B:50)
        - Easter Offerings (Box I:B:50)
        - Elberon Church (Box I:B:50)
        - Employment Committee (Box I:B:50)
        - Faith is the Answer (Box I:B:50)
        - Foreign Mail (Box I:B:50)
        - Guide to Confident Living Serial in Newspaper, correspondence (Box I:B:50)
        - Guide to Confident Living (Box I:B:51)
        - Harriman, Mrs. Grace (Box I:B:51)
        - Illustrations (Box I:B:52)
        - Kansas City Star (Box I:B:52)
        - Ketchum, Milton D. (Box I:B:52)
        - Madison Square Garden (Box I:B:52)
        - Midwood Lodge (Box I:B:52)
        - Men's League (Box I:B:52)
        - Miami Herald (Box I:B:52)
        - Miller, O.R. (Box I:B:52)
        - Not Death at All (Box I:B:52)
        - Notes on Lecture Engagements (Box I:B:52)
        - Pastor's Purse (Box I:B:52)
        - Pawling (Box I:B:52)
        - Peale Family (Box I:B:52)
        - Peale, Dr. C.C. (Box I:B:52)
        - Peale, Rev. Leonard (Box I:B:52)
        - Peale, Norman, personal (Box I:B:52)
        - Peale, Mrs. Norman (Box I:B:52)
        - Peale, Mrs. Norman, correspondence (Box I:B:52)
        - Peale, Dr. Robert C. (Box I:B:52)
        - Peat, Harold (Box I:B:53)
        - Peck, George (Box I:B:53)
        - Philadelphia Enquirer (Box I:B:53)
        - Pittsburg Post Gazette (Box I:B:53)
        - Post-Hall Syndicate, Inc., Robert M. Hall (Box I:B:53)
        - Prentice-Hall (Box I:B:53)
        - Presbyterian Minister's Fund (Box I:B:53)
        - Recording Instruments (Box I:B:53)
        - References (Box I:B:53)
        - Reformed Church (Box I:B:53)
        - Reprints of Articles (Box I:B:53)
        - Rotary (Box I:B:53)
        - Rotary International, Sun. June 12 (Box I:B:54)
        - St. Nicholas (Box I:B:54)
        - S.H. Scott Problem (Box I:B:54)
        - Seating Difficulties, Letters re: (Box I:B:54)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, A-I (Box I:B:54)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, J-Z (Box I:B:55)
        - Special Work Committee (Box I:B:55)
        - Spiritual Mobilization (Box I:B:55)
        - Staff Memos (Box I:B:56)
        - Stafford Family (Box I:B:56)
        - Summer Supplies (Box I:B:56)
        - Sunday Memos (Box I:B:56)
        - Sunday Visitors (Box I:B:56)
        - Syndicate (Newspaper) Correspondence with Howard D. Wheeler, etc. (Box I:B:56)
        - Syndicated Column, "Confident Living" (Box I:B:56)
        - Syndicate Material, K.S. Giniger (Box I:B:56)
        - Western College (Box I:B:56)
        - Woman's Home Companion (Box I:B:56)
        - Woodbury, Clarence (Box I:B:56)
        - Y.M.C.A. (Box I:B:56)
      - Correspondence, 1950
        - Advertising (Box I:B:57)
        - America's Future, Request for Dr. Peale Reprint (II) Program #43 (Box I:B:57)
        - Anonymous (Box I:B:57)
        - Apartments N.V.P. (Box I:B:57)
        - Art of Real Happiness (Box I:B:57)
        - Birthday Letters (Box I:B:57)
        - Blanton, Dr. Smiley (Box I:B:57)
        - Books (Box I:B:58)
        - Budget (Box I:B:58)
        - Christian Freedom Foundation, Inc. (Box I:B:58)
        - Christmas Offering (Box I:B:58)
        - Citizen's Committee for Children and Youth (Box I:B:58)
        - Citizen's Committee for Children and Youth (Box I:B:59)
        - Classis (Box I:B:59)
        - Clinic (Box I:B:59)
        - Collegiate Church (Box I:B:59)
        - Column Clippings (Box I:B:59)
        - Column Correspondence (Box I:B:59)
        - Commission on Chaplains (Box I:B:60)
        - Committee for Constitutional Government (Box I:B:60)
        - Consistory (Box I:B:60)
        - Deerfield Academy (Box I:B:60)
        - Dicker, Gerald (Box I:B:60)
        - Easter (Box I:B:60)
        - Employment (Box I:B:60)
        - Faith is the Answer (Box I:B:60)
        - F.B.I. (Box I:B:60)
        - Flint, Maurice (Box I:B:60)
        - Foreign Mail (Box I:B:60)
        - Guide to Confident Living (Box I:B:60)
        - Guide to Confident Living Serial (Box I:B:60)
        - Hanley - Dewey Matter (Letters Re:) (Box I:B:60)
        - Houlberg, Miss Rita (Box I:B:60)
        - Illustrations (Box I:B:60)
        - Ketchum, Milton D. (Box I:B:60)
        - Lake Mohonk (Box I:B:61)
        - Lenten and Easter Material (Box I:B:61)
        - Look Magazine (Box I:B:61)
        - Marble Club (Box I:B:61)
        - Men's League (Box I:B:61)
        - Midcentury White House Conference on Children and Youth (Box I:B:61)
        - Midwood Lodge (Box I:B:61)
        - New Members (Box I:B:61)
        - Newspapers - "Guide to Confident Living" (Box I:B:61)
        - "Not Death at All" (Box I:B:61)
        - Pastor's Purse (Box I:B:61)
        - Pawling (Box I:B:61)
        - Peale Family (Box I:B:61)
        - Peale, Dr. C.C. (Box I:B:61)
        - Peale, Elizabeth (Box I:B:61)
        - Peale, John S. (Box I:B:61)
        - Peale, Rev. Leonard (Box I:B:61)
        - Peale, Margaret (Box I:B:61)
        - Peale, Dr. Norman Vincent, personal (Box I:B:61)
        - Peale, Mrs. Norman Vincent (Box I:B:62)
        - Peale, Dr. Robert C. (Box I:B:62)
        - Peale, Mr. Robert W (Box I:B:62)
        - Peale, Mr. William F. (Box I:B:62)
        - Peat, Mr. Harold R. (Box I:B:62)
        - Peck, George (Box I:B:62)
        - Post-Hall Syndicate (Box I:B:62)
        - Prentice Hall (Box I:B:62)
        - Presbyterian Minister's Fund (Box I:B:62)
        - Rainbow Ranch For Boys (Box I:B:62)
        - Reader's Digest (Box I:B:62)
        - References (Box I:B:63)
        - Reformed Church (Box I:B:63)
        - Rotary Club (Box I:B:63)
        - Rumely, Dr. Edward A. (Box I:B:63)
        - St. Nicholas Collegiate Church (Box I:B:63)
        - Seating Problem (Box I:B:63)
        - Serialization, Art of Real Happiness (Box I:B:63)
        - Sons of the American Revolution (Box I:B:63)
        - Special Work Committee (Box I:B:63)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, A-C (Box I:B:63)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, D-Z (Box I:B:64)
        - Special Work Committee (Box I:B:65)
        - Spiritual Mobilization (Box I:B:65)
        - Spiritual Mobilization Luncheon (Box I:B:65)
        - Staff Memos (Box I:B:65)
        - Stafford Family (Box I:B:65)
        - Summer Supplies (Box I:B:65)
        - Sunday Visitors (Box I:B:66)
        - Syndicated Column (Box I:B:66)
        - Syndicated Columns, Jan-Dec (Box I:B:66)
        - Television (Box I:B:67)
        - Western College for Women (Box I:B:67)
        - Whitefield, New Hampshire (Box I:B:67)
        - Young Adults (Box I:B:67)
        - Y.M.C.A. (Box I:B:67)
      - Correspondence, 1951
        - Advertising (Box I:B:67)
        - America's Future - Requests for Dr. Peale Reprint Program #43 (Box I:B:67)
        - Anonymous (Box I:B:67)
        - Apartment at Forty-Fifth Avenue (Box I:B:67)
        - Art of Living (Box I:B:67)
        - Art of Living, File Copies (Box I:B:67)
        - Art of Living, Extra Copies (Box I:B:68)
        - Art of Real Happiness (Box I:B:68)
        - Birthday Letters (Box I:B:68)
        - Blanton, Dr. Smiley (Box I:B:68)
        - Books (Box I:B:68)
        - Broadcasting and Film Commission (Box I:B:69)
        - Budget (Box I:B:69)
        - Christian Economics (Box I:B:69)
        - Christian Freedom Foundation, Inc (Box I:B:69)
        - Christmas Cards (Box I:B:69)
        - Christmas Offering (Box I:B:69)
        - Citizens Committee of 100 for Children and Youth (Box I:B:69)
        - Classis (Box I:B:69)
        - Clinic (Box I:B:69)
        - Collegiate Church (Box I:B:69)
        - Column Clippings (Box I:B:69)
        - Column Correspondence (Box I:B:69)
        - Column Correspondence - Faith Healing (Box I:B:70)
        - Column Correspondence - "A Soldier's Dilemma" (Box I:B:70)
        - Comments (Box I:B:70)
        - Commission on Chaplains (Box I:B:70)
        - Committee for Constitutional Government (Box I:B:70)
        - Consistory (Box I:B:70)
        - Deerfield Academy (Box I:B:70)
        - Dickler, Gerald (Box I:B:70)
        - Easter (Box I:B:70)
        - Employment (Box I:B:70)
        - Faith is the Answer (Box I:B:70)
        - Fifth avenue - 1030 Fifth Ave. (Box I:B:70)
        - Foreign Mail (Box I:B:71)
        - Girls' Town, Inc. - Mrs. Gertrude Wixson (Box I:B:71)
        - "Guide to Confident Living" (Box I:B:71)
        - Houlberg, Miss Rita (Box I:B:71)
        - Illustrations (Box I:B:71)
        - Ketchum, Milton D. (Box I:B:71)
        - Langstadter Tax Matter (Box I:B:71)
        - Marble Club (Box I:B:71)
        - Masonic Lodge (Box I:B:71)
        - Men's League (Box I:B:71)
        - Misc. (Box I:B:71)
        - New Members (Box I:B:71)
        - Pastor's Purse (Box I:B:71)
        - Pawling (Box I:B:71)
        - Peale Family (Box I:B:71)
        - Peale, Dr. C.C. (Box I:B:71)
        - Peale, John S. (Box I:B:71)
        - Peale, Rev. Leonard (Box I:B:71)
        - Peale, Margaret (Box I:B:71)
        - Peale, Dr. Norman V., personal
        - Peale/Oursler Column (Box I:B:71)
        - Peale, Mrs. Norman V. (Box I:B:72)
        - Peale, Dr. Robert C. (Box I:B:72)
        - Peale, Mr. Robert W (Box I:B:72)
        - Peale, Mr. William F. (Box I:B:72)
        - Peat, Mr. Harold R. (Box I:B:72)
        - Post-Hall Syndicate (Box I:B:72)
        - Prentice-Hall (Box I:B:72)
        - Presbyterian Minister's Fund (Box I:B:72)
        - Protestant Radio Commission (Box I:B:72)
        - Radio Program (Box I:B:72)
        - Reader's Digest (Box I:B:72)
        - References (Box I:B:72)
        - Reformed Church (Box I:B:72)
        - Rotary Club (Box I:B:72)
        - Rumely, Dr. Edward A. (Box I:B:72)
        - St. Nicholas Collegiate Church (Box I:B:72)
        - Seating Problems (Box I:B:72)
        - Soldier's Dilemma (Box I:B:72)
        - Sons of American Revolution (Box I:B:72)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, A-O (Box I:B:73)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, P-Z (Box I:B:74)
        - Special Works Committee (Box I:B:74)
        - Spiritual Mobilization (Box I:B:74)
        - Staff Memos (Box I:B:74)
        - Stafford Family (Box I:B:74)
        - Summer Supplies (Box I:B:74)
        - Sunday Visitors (Box I:B:74)
        - Syndicated Column (Box I:B:75)
        - Syndicated Columns Release, Jan-Dec (Box I:B:75)
        - Television (Box I:B:75)
        - Western College for Women (Box I:B:75)
        - You Can Win (Box I:B:75)
      - Correspondence, 1952
        - Advertising (Box I:B:75)
        - American Humane Assoc. (Box I:B:75)
        - Mr. Anders - Treasurer (Box I:B:76)
        - Anonymous (Box I:B:76)
        - Birthday Letters (Box I:B:76)
        - Blanton, Dr. Smiley (Box I:B:76)
        - Books (Box I:B:76)
        - Bookstores in Various Cities (Box I:B:76)
        - Broadcasting and Film (Box I:B:76)
        - Budget (Box I:B:76)
        - Burkhart, Roy (Box I:B:77)
        - Christian Freedom Foundation (Box I:B:77)
        - Classis (Box I:B:77)
        - Clinic (Box I:B:77)
        - Collegiate Church (Box I:B:77)
        - Column Clippings (Box I:B:77)
        - Column Correspondence (Box I:B:77)
        - Commission on Chaplains (Box I:B:77)
        - Committee for Constitutional Government (Box I:B:77)
        - Consistory (Box I:B:77)
        - Deerfield Academy (Box I:B:77)
        - Dickler, Gerald (Box I:B:77)
        - Easter Offerings (Box I:B:78)
        - Easter Tickets, Requests for (Box I:B:78)
        - Employment (Box I:B:78)
        - Faith is the Answer (Box I:B:78)
        - Girls' Town Inc. - Mrs. Gertrude Wixson (Box I:B:78)
        - "Guide to Confident Living" (Box I:B:78)
        - Horatio Alger Award (Box I:B:78)
        - Ketchum, Milton D. (Box I:B:78)
        - Marble Club (Box I:B:78)
        - Masonic Lodge (Box I:B:78)
        - Newspapers Carrying Column, "Guide to Confident Living" (Box I:B:78)
        - Men's League (Box I:B:78)
        - Ohio Friends (Box I:B:78)
        - Ohio Society at New York (Box I:B:78)
        - Pawling (Box I:B:79)
        - Peale Family (Box I:B:79)
        - Peale, Dr. C.C. (Box I:B:79)
        - Peale, Mr. John S. (Box I:B:79)
        - Peale, Mr. Leonard O. (Box I:B:79)
        - Peale, Margaret (Box I:B:79)
        - Peale, Norman V., personal (Box I:B:79)
        - Peale, Mrs. Norman V. (Box I:B:79)
        - Peale - Oursler Columns (Box I:B:79)
        - Peale, Dr. Robert C. (Box I:B:79)
        - Peale, Mr. Robert W. (Box I:B:79)
        - Peale, Mr. William F. (Box I:B:79)
        - Post-Hall Syndicate (Box I:B:79)
        - Prentice-Hall (Box I:B:79)
        - Presbyterian Ministers' Fund (Box I:B:79)
        - References (Box I:B:79)
        - Reformed Church (Box I:B:79)
        - Rotary Club (Box I:B:79)
        - Rumely, Dr. Edward (Box I:B:79)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, A-O (Box I:B:80)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, P-Z (Box I:B:81)
        - Special Work Committee (Box I:B:81)
        - Spiritual Mobilization (Box I:B:81)
        - Staff Memos (Box I:B:81)
        - Stafford Family (Box I:B:81)
        - Summer Supplies (Box I:B:81)
        - Sunday Visitors (Box I:B:81)
        - Syndicated Columns, Jan-Aug (Box I:B:82)
        - Television (Box I:B:82)
        - Testimonial Dinner (Box I:B:82)
        - 20th Anniversary (Box I:B:82)
        - Western College for Women (Box I:B:82)
        - Who's Who (Box I:B:82)
        - Advertising (Box I:B:82)
        - Mr. Anders - Treasurer (Box I:B:82)
        - Anonymous (Box I:B:83)
        - Art of Living (Box I:B:83)
        - Broadcasting and Film Commission (Box I:B:83)
        - Committee for Constitutional Government (Box I:B:83)
        - Confident Living (Box I:B:83)
        - Consistory (Box I:B:83)
        - Deerfield Academy (Box I:B:83)
        - Dickler, Gerald (Box I:B:83)
        - Easter Cards (Box I:B:83)
        - Easter Offerings (Box I:B:83)
        - Easter Tickets (Box I:B:83)
        - Employment (Box I:B:83)
        - Dep't of Evangelism (Box I:B:83)
        - Facts Forum (Box I:B:83)
        - Faith is the Answer (Box I:B:83)
        - Freedoms Foundation (Box I:B:83)
        - Dr. Peale's Genealogy, correspondence with Mrs. Florence Dickinson (Box I:B:83)
        - Girls' Town Inc. - Mrs. Gertrude Wixson (Box I:B:84)
        - Dr. Howard Gist (Box I:B:84)
        - Guide to Confident Living (Box I:B:84)
        - Guideposts (Box I:B:84)
        - Men's League (Box I:B:84)
        - Ohio Friends (Box I:B:84)
        - Ohio Society of New York (Box I:B:84)
        - Ohio Wesleyan (Box I:B:85)
        - People to Contact in Various Cities (Box I:B:85)
        - The Power of Positive Thinking (copies to be mailed out) (Box I:B:85)
        - Readers Digest (Box I:B:86)
        - Testimonials (Box I:B:86)
        - Western College for Women (Box I:B:86)
        - Achor, L.B. (Box I:B:86)